seovalidator.net 2012-06-10

# SEOValidator.Net - Search Engine Optimization Tool and SEO Tips - Privacy

At SEOVALIDATOR, we are keenly aware of the trust you place in us and it is our responsibility to protect your privacy. As a part of this responsibility, we let you know what information we collect when you use our website analysis tool, why we collect it and how we use it to improve your experience. By using the SEOVALIDATOR web tool, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Information Collection

Every data collected by SEOVALIDATOR tool can be manually accessed by several other means publicly available online (Whois Lookup, Google Cached Pages, etc.). That's why every single report generated on SEOVALIDATOR.NET is considered 'public' and is thus stored in our database. Furthermore it can be indexed by search engines.

SEOVALIDATOR collects and uses website information to operate its website analysis tool and deliver the services you have requested. This information can include: IP address, domain names, estimated visitors, in-site and off-site SEO analysis, usability, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by SEOVALIDATOR for the operation of its service and to provide general statistics regarding use of SEOVALIDATOR web tool.

### Use of Personal Information

If you subscribe to the newsletter SEOVALIDATOR may use your personally identifiable email to inform you of other products or services available from SEOVALIDATOR and its affiliates. SEOVALIDATOR may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through SEOVALIDATOR blog, this information may be collected and used by others.

SEOVALIDATOR does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. SEOVALIDATOR may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, SEOVALIDATOR may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SEOVALIDATOR, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

SEOVALIDATOR web tools will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SEOVALIDATOR or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SEOVALIDATOR (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SEOVALIDATOR, or the public.

### Security of your Personal Information

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. SEOVALIDATOR uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. SEOVALIDATOR secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Changes to this Statement

SEOVALIDATOR will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SEOVALIDATOR encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SEOVALIDATOR is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date below.
